Rough Rough Members 2-shot Talk
This corner will be done by just two members.
Best regards, and thank you very much for your cooperation.
Today's guest is this person.
Yes, I am Yui Akanashi. Nice to meet you.
Please give my best regards. This is Yui Yui.
I nominated her.
I have to nominate Yui Yui at the end of this corner.
How do you like it? Have you chosen?
I'm not sure.
Lost?
I can't choose.
First question.
What was your impression when you first saw them?
First of all, Rurun's answer was that the first person I talked to when I went to the audition site was Yui Yui.
What?
When I entered the waiting room, Menya and Arisachi were right in front of me and I was standing there because I was so nervous.
I remember YuiYui said in a kind voice, "You can sit down.
I also remember this.
What?
Harurun was standing there and I was shy.
I was also sparkling.
Then Yui Yui said, "That was Yui Yui.
I don't remember.
You don't remember?
I really don't remember.
Really?
Really? Did I do that?
At first, I had an image of Monami as a kind and gentle, legitimate older sister with a good style, but on the second day of the audition, I saw her imitating Shiri and thought it might be interesting.
But on the second day of the audition, I saw her imitating Shiri, and I thought it might be interesting.
I'm messing with her a little bit.
She was doing her impersonations and teasing others at the same time.
But it's still very mature.
That's right. Like a big sister.
Yes, she is.
Meinachan. It says "Meinachan.
Meinachan?
Meini-chan.
She's a sweet girl who cries when she sees other girls come home from the audition crying because they've been praised.
The more I got to know her, the more I thought she was a strange girl.
It says she wasn't a quiet girl.
If it says she was, then she wasn't.
No, but I think she is a natural.
I think she's cute and outgoing.
Next, we asked them to describe Yui Yui in one word.
Unexpectedly strange sister. This one came from Miririn.
Surprising.
I thought she would be a little different.
What did you expect?
Oh, my God, I thought it was going to be a kouhou pang.
Koho.
That's what I really said.
You're a strange girl.
And Ryoka is a kouhou sister with a perfect style and face.
She has it all.
That's amazing. I'm a little embarrassed.
And then there's Miku. Kouhou, the hot and spicy one, is a drink.
Hot and spicy is a drink. That's right. That's it. You didn't make the curry drink very hot, did you?
You eat it without water, right?
Maybe it is indeed a drink.
It's me. From me.
You're always sleepy, my trusty big sister.
It's getting worse lately. You say you want to sleep all the time.
I want to sleep all the time.
I am the eldest of three sisters and I don't have an older sister, so I am very happy that YuiYui is like an older sister to me.
That's right. You are the eldest of three sisters at home, right?
So when I am down, she pats me on the head, talks to me about things, and I like her very much because she is a person I can trust.
When I'm crying, patting me on the head makes me cry more.
That's right. I don't often get spoiled by other people, so I feel a little vulnerable when they do this to me.
That's right. The other day, when I played head-bumps with her, she was already spoiled.
Next was a questionnaire asking, "What is the yui yui that only you know? The next question is, "What is the yui yui that only you know?
What do you think? First of all, Ryoka.
Ryoka, what would you say?
Ryoka's answer is that she often has professional discussions about beauty with her makeup artist. When she eats, she eats a lot.
That's right. Eats well and talks a lot.
That's right. You like makeup a lot, don't you?
I like it.
Some of the girls talk a lot.
I'm not so good at air arranging my hair as I am at making up my face, so I had the makeup artist do it for me today.
You heard that today, right?
That's right. The ribbon is here now, but would you like it a little lower? I ask her "Which side do you want the ribbon on?
Which side would you like the ribbon on? I asked them.
That's right. The right side is better? I was like, "Which side is better?
Yes, I did.
I ask so many questions.
Next, Meinya.
What do you say, Meino-chan? She eats a lot.
You eat a lot, too, don't you, Meino?
I have an image of her always eating something even though she is thin. Everyone else eats a piece of bread for a light meal, but she eats a piece of bread and two rice balls, which is obviously a lot of food. I wonder why she is so thin.
It sounds like an essay.
Really. I can't catch up with them at the end.
When I'm hungry, I expect everything I do to last a lifetime, and it's like my activity limit.
I don't talk when I'm hungry.
I don't talk. When I ask, "Are you feeling sick? I asked her if she was feeling sick.
He said, "I'm hungry.
I have to eat. I can't do it.
I see. Then eat a lot more.
Okay? From now on.
I'm thin.
I'll eat a lot.
Please eat.Please eat.
Yay.
Then, to Miri.
Miri?
Miri's cheeks are surprisingly soft.
They are soft, aren't they?
Like mochi (rice cakes).
Everyone who touches them is surprised.
They're so shiny,
I was surprised that they were so much softer than I imagined.
It's softer than I expected.
It's my charm point. Actually.
The other day, when Miri touched my cheek,
She said there was a bone, and tried to touch the bone in the back,
It hurt so much.
She said, "There's a bone! He said, "There is a bone!
He was trying to go deep into the skin.
I was scared, scared, scared.
There is a bone.
Yes, I have bones.
Next, Miku.
I don't want Mikuni to open a folding umbrella instead of a microphone.
A microphone?
Uh, microphone stand-in.
If you use a folding umbrella as a microphone during practice,
She doesn't like it when it opens,
I use a toothpaste set.
You don't want me to open the toothpaste set.
I say.
When I don't have enough microphones during practice, I use a dummy microphone,
I use a dummy mic.
People usually use a comb or a drink or something.
Most of them use plastic bottles,
Plastic bottles are heavy, aren't they?
I heard that this kind of thing happens a lot.
That's why I carry a toothbrush set every day,
I sing like this with my toothbrush set,
If the lid comes off, the toothbrush pops out.
I'm very careful.
You know, when you shake the toothbrush case, the toothbrush makes a sound.
How to brush your teeth.
When you move your feet, it makes a clacking sound.
I can easily tell where he is.
I know, I know, I know.
Next, Monami.
For some reason, it seems there are a lot of Ruff Ruff fans at Itchy's university.
There are people watching Ruff Ruff's YouTube, and they call out to me.
But to her father, she is active as Ruff Ruff,
I don't think he knew I was working as Ruff Ruff for a couple of months.
That's right.
But college, did I mention?
With Poo-chan,
I don't know if I ever told you in front of the camera,
I'm taking the entrance exam for college,
You know how you introduce yourself in front of everyone?
I'm Yui Takanashi, a senior in college.
I will do my best.
They asked me about my hobbies,
I said I like to listen to the radio,
The teacher asked me, "Whose radio do you like? He asked me who's radio I like,
I told him that I really like the radio of a TV producer named Nobuyuki Sakama.
I told him that I really liked the radio show of a TV producer, Nobuyuki Sakama, and then he sat down,
I was sitting in the group work, and I was talking with the person next to me,
Are you from Ruff Ruff? He said, "I saw this!
He said, "I saw this! I said, "I saw this!
I thought, "You're going to do this! I was so surprised.
I was surprised, wasn't I?
And then they looked at me like, "Do it! They looked at me like, "Do it!
I thought, "I'm going to do it.
I wonder if he's watching me right now?
I wonder if he's giving me a BJ?
He said, "I'm doing it right now.
I'm doing it.
I'm Marin.
Surprise, surprise.
And then there were the lectures at the university,
In a university lecture room, there are steps like in a movie theater,
The guy in front of me was on that step,
When I watch YouTube, it's amazing to see Ruff Ruff doing his big comedy.
I'd sneak in and watch it during class.
Watching it in class,
What? There he is! I'm here!
I'm right there! I'm right there!
I don't call out to them.
I might see them.
I don't tell him that,
It's amazing that they really just like to watch.
It's amazing.
I know, I saw a boy from my school looking at me,
He was grinning at me like this.
So you mean he looked at you?
You don't like it? That boy.
I don't think so.
Maybe he's watching you. I'm doing it, Fuu.
That was shocking, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
Next, I asked, "What's the most amazing part? I'll ask you.
This part is great?
Meyan.
When it comes to radio broadcasting, I think it's the earnestness and hard work,When it comes to seriousness and effort goes on the radio,
Listen to an endless variety of radio,
If episodic talk becomes difficult,
I take notes of episodes that I can use on a daily basis.
And when it comes to gravitating work, he squeezes,
He is also ahead of the curve when it comes to radio work and YouTube,
She is stoic anyway.
I think she would be happy to hear that from Meina-chan.
A 10-year player in the entertainment industry.
That's right. You are my senior, right?
You are my senior.
I really respect you, but on the contrary, I look up to you. Meina-chan.
You call yourself a stoic.
That makes me happy.
I'm glad.
I really think so.
Before a live concert, I sometimes feel like my face is really sharper.
Really?
Yes, I do.
I'm glad.
I'm after the show now, so I wonder if it's still there. Maybe.
No, I'm just shuffling.
Next.
Arisuke.
I often counsel him.
I often give advice to high school students.
Twice.
I'm writing this twice because it's important.
I think it's because everyone thinks that Yui is kind and reliable.
Consulting.
But I think it's more like we're both riding on each other's coattails and being ridden by each other,
But if I can make it easier for them to do their activities by listening to them, I would like to listen to them.
I'm glad to hear that. Thank you very much.
I hope you will continue to do so.
Thank you.
Next.
Monamin.
Yui has a strong image of being a candidate for Ruff Ruff, but she has a very beautiful singing voice.
Especially during live performances, her voice is very loud and her sound is very stable, and she is one of the members who support RAFRAF's singing ability.
What do you think? I don't have much confidence in my performance.
No way!
I love Yui Yui's singing voice. I was talking with my mom and others.
I was at the very beginning, so I wasn't Yui Yui yet.
Yui.
She said, "Yui, you are a great singer.
I was happy.
She was talking to her mother.
Really?
But I think most of the members of Rough Rough are good at low-pitched parts, and since it's the other way around, I thought we could cover for each other.
I can play high notes, but I can't play low notes at all.
I see.
Non-chan is on this side. You have high notes.
I can only produce high notes.
You still do, don't you?
What's the last part of "Marriage Refused"?
The part where she says, "Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee!"?
Yeah.
I love that part.
I've heard a lot of replies on Twitter from fans saying that the last part was really good.
I really like that part.
Thank you so much.
Please continue to support my singing ability.
I'll do my best to get better.
Next, Ryo-ka.
This way.
Her knowledge of beauty is amazing. Her ability to maintain her style. Her out-view beauty is getting better. Her singing voice is beautiful. Perfect pitch control. She is good at talking and listening and easy to talk to.
She's already written a lot.
Ryoka-chan.
She praises me a lot.
That's great.
I might get embarrassed.
But I think it's all true.
Really?
That's great.
I'll do my best.
Let's do our best.
All right.
Next. Is there anything you honestly want me to fix?
You're going up and down. It's going up and being brought down.
There are a lot of things.
The first three guys are saying almost the same thing.
What?
What? I'm scared.
Hayashi, Sasaki, Saito.
What is it?
When you get sleepy, your soul goes somewhere else.
When you are in an important discussion, please do your best to stay awake. Sometimes it seems like you are listening but you are not.
I will do my best. I am sorry.
I am so sorry.
I lose consciousness when I'm sleepy.
Spring is a dawn, isn't it?
Especially recently, right? I've been busy with gigs.
No, I'll be up in a bit. I'll get up.
I'll get up. I'll do my best.
I'll be careful.
Manami.
When members are not sure whether to eat spicy food or not, they sometimes tell me that it was not spicy, but the information from Yui, who loves very spicy food, is not helpful at all.
Everyone just listens to that and always gives me a "pooh-pooh" when they hear about it.Yes, people always pooh-pooh me for just listening to that story.
I'll give it a try.
Okay, let's go.
I don't eat much spicy food.
I don't eat spicy food.
I don't eat spicy food with gummy bears.
That's right. Job-hunting gummies.
There are two answers for every day.
Oh, there are two?
The first. When I pass by a spicy noodle shop or a cafe, they try to take me there. Please don't do that.
The second one. He drinks a lot of water. The water in the office was running out fast, and the culprit was Yuichan.
Yui, who consumes about four bottles of water a day, feels sorry for him and has recently brought several plastic bottles with her.
It is fulfilling, isn't it? It's hard, as everyone says, but he drinks a lot of water, and he knows it.
It's amazing, isn't it?
When everyone is still drinking one bottle, there are two or three empty bottles on the table.
The rule was that you could freely take water from the office.
But it was obvious that the water was running low, and when I asked, "Who are you? I took about two bottles a day, and then I got scolded, so I took up to one bottle a day.
The rule was changed.
Sometimes dance lessons were long, about 8 hours long.
I had to carry four 500ml plastic bottles with me, so I had to breathe heavily.
And you walk a lot.
Yes, I take walks, like between stations. I drink a lot. I breathe very heavily, but I feel light on the way back home.
I drink everything.
The last thing I want to say.
Arisatchi asked me a question. Is there any spicy food you would like to try?
Oh, very spicy.
I'm from Chiba Prefecture, but I forgot the name.
What was it?
There is a ramen restaurant along the Toyo Expressway in Chiba,
There is a famous spicy ramen restaurant along the Toyo Expressway in Chiba, I want to go there so badly, I forgot its name.
I forgot the name.
If you remember it, this will come up and you can tell him on Twitter.
It's so frustrating.
I was looking it up yesterday.
I'll go next time.
Sorry I didn't wake you up when Yui was sleeping on the train.
It's Haru.
I'll wake you up from now on.
You recognized me right away, didn't you? It's Haru-chan.
Yes, I did. But, I don't know, when I really fall asleep, I don't wake up.
So I thought maybe Haru-chan woke me up but left me there because I was sleeping so much.
That's true.
I don't wake up when I fall asleep.
I don't know.
I was taking my medicine. And I miss the bus.
From now on, I'm going to have to wake you up.
I'm responding.
I'm falling.
I'll do my best.
Next, from Mikun.
If I had to say so, I'd say don't lose any more weight.
Feelings? The way you drew Miku.
The pictograms are there, too.
Can I just look at the pictograms?
Oh, really!
Middy.
Ui-chan has a habit of whispering, right?
Do I? You do?
I thought I was pretty loud in Ruff Ruff.
But you were talking to yourself yesterday.
Yeah, I guess.
You're pretty loud when you talk like this.
But you're also loud when you talk by yourself.
The other day, we went to the dance practice room.
At that time
"Oh, what's the line of flow here?" I was like, "Oh, what was the line of flow here?
And I was blabbing on and on and on.
Meina-chan said to me, "What did you say?" And Meina-chan said to me.
"What? By yourself?" and I'm saying it at this volume, so...
I see.
Yeah, I think it's probably big enough for one person, too.
What?
It's so tiny.
Is your voice quieter in front of Miri?
Are you nervous? Not yet.
Mi-chan, Mi-chan has a big voice.
Yes, that's true.
And so our first two-shot talk was over.
Our first two-shot talk is over.
How was it?
It was a lot of fun.
We talked about all kinds of things.
I'm worried I talked a little too much.
I want to talk more.
And since it's a relay system
YuiYui has to nominate next.
Is there a member you'd like to nominate?
Okay, I've decided.
The next person for the relay talk...
Riki Fujisaki.
I like her.
It's been a while since we've been close.
We're the Chiba duo, and we're also in Kairimisu together.
That's right. We always have the image of being together.
Yay!
Next time, Yui Yui and Mi-kun
we will have a twishot talk!
That's all for now.
This is the members' relay talk.This was a member relay talk.
Thank you very much.
Good morning!
I am Mai Niinouchi. Pleased to meet you.
I'm Mai Shinnai, and it's nice to meet you.
Are you self-producing properly?
Oh, my!
What is this? What is this?
My favorite Osaka girl, Hayashi, just cried!
Who was your guess, Hayashi?
27 years old.
No!
Thanks again for watching to the end!
What did you think of today's episode?
Hey, did you enjoy it?
What did you like?
Hey, tell me the truth!
I'm not mad at you, just tell me the truth!
I'm not mad at you! I'm not mad!
Yeah, I'm not mad!
Let me know what you think in the comments section or on Twitter!
Write it down! Please!
Please!